Geek vs Chic. Beauty vs Beast. Downtown vs Uptown. What
happens when three sets of BFF's become enemies?
Frenemies is a drama, family, tv movie film
directed by Daisy von Scherler Mayer.
Three pairs of friends relationships go from good to bad and back again.
Several couple fall out over girls, boys and work.
Can all these couples settle their differences and be friends again?
Avalon Greene, played by Bella Thorne.
Halley Brandon, played by Zendaya.
Savannah O'Neal / Emma Reynolds, played by Mary Mouser.
Jake Logan, played by Nick Robinson.
Julianne, played by Stefanie Scott.
Walker, played by Connor Price.
Frenemies is a 2012 teen comedy-drama anthology television film
based on the novel of the same name by Alexa Young.
It features an ensemble cast starring Bella Thorne, Zendaya, Stefanie Scott, Nick Robinson, Mary Mouser (in a
dual role) and features Connor Price, Jascha Washington (in his final film role) and Dylan Everett.
The film follows three pairs of teenage friends that go from friends to enemies and back again: two girls who run a
fashion blog, a boy and his dog, and a tomboy who trades places with an uptown girl who looks like her twin.
The film was directed by Daisy Mayer and written by
Dava Savel, Wendy Weiner, and Jim Krieg.
The Disney Channel Original Movie premiered on January
13, 2012, in the United States and Canada.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or book,
teen comedy, multiple storylines, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.